<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our-schools on Harmony Primary School</title>
    <link>/our-school/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our-schools on Harmony Primary School</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="/our-school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our Governors</title>
      <link>/our-school/our-governors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/our-governors/</guid>
      <description>Governors Role The role of the Governing Body is an intrinsic part of the leadership of the school, although often unseen by parents and other community stakeholders. We are here to oversee the school is providing the best for your child to the best of their capabilities. This impact statement is one way in which the Governing Body articulates their role in school leadership, the impact we have had on school improvement, and been transparent about their activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Vision</title>
      <link>/our-school/our-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/our-vision/</guid>
      <description>Our Mission Harmony Primary School aims to bring out the best in each individual, striving for excellence on a daily basis; at HPS we lay down strong academic roots as our children are enriched by a broad, balanced curriculum that nurtures their abilities. Our school harmoniously bring together our children, parents &amp;amp; educators to cultivate an inspiring learning experience rooted in an Islamic ethos.
Harmony Primary School Prospectus  Our Ethos Harmony Primary School is an Islamic faith school which follows the Sunni methodology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Administrator Job Description</title>
      <link>/our-school/vacancies/school-administrator-job-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/vacancies/school-administrator-job-description/</guid>
      <description>School Administrator          Post title: School Administrator   Responsible to: The Headteacher and Governing Body   Status: Permanent/Full time and Part-Time (Part-time 0.5 Term-time only)   Pay: Competitive    How to apply To apply for this position, download and fill out the application form, and send it to us at the following email address: admin@harmonyprimaryschool.co.uk
Application Form  Our Mission Harmony Primary School aims to bring out the best in each individual, striving for excellence on a daily basis; at HPS we lay down strong academic roots as our children are enriched by a broad, balanced curriculum that nurtures their abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff</title>
      <link>/our-school/our-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/our-staff/</guid>
      <description>Our Harmony Team Come and meet the staff at our school.
From parents and guardians, to support staff and teachers, we&amp;rsquo;re here to help students flourish. But not one of us could do it alone.
As a school striving for Excellence in Education we are delighted to get to know you better and join the vibrant local community of Harrow and North West London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff Vacancies</title>
      <link>/our-school/staff-vacancies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/staff-vacancies/</guid>
      <description>Staff Vacancies Thank you for your interest in Harmony Primary School.
We currently do not have any vacancies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
