<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Harmony Primary School</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Harmony Primary School</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Apply</title>
      <link>/admissions/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/admissions/apply/</guid>
      <description>Apply The formal applications process will commence upon successful registration with the DfE. However, parents are encouraged to complete the Expression of Interest form in the first instance.
Once the school is operational our applications process will include an Entry Test for all children from year 1 to Year 6, if the child is able to successfully complete this assessment set by the school, then an informal interview with your child and the parents will be arranged with a view to offering a place within our school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessment</title>
      <link>/curriculum/assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/curriculum/assessment/</guid>
      <description>Assessment The National Curriculum has been written to give Age Related Expectations (ARE) for the end of each year. As children travel from Year 1 to Year 6 in our school, they are tracked against the Age Related Expectations. At Harmony Primary School we use RM Integris to support our tracking, the provided us with numbered bands and steps to track children.
The school reports to parents three times a year, at parents evenings you will receive your child&amp;rsquo;s targets based on the RM Integris curriculum linked statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class Teacher Job Description</title>
      <link>/our-school/vacancies/class-teacher-job-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/vacancies/class-teacher-job-description/</guid>
      <description>Class Teacher          Post title: Primary School Teacher – KS1/KS2   Responsible to: The Headteacher and Governing Body   Status: Permanent   Pay: Subject to experience   Additional benefits: Training and Development allowanceSupport with pursuing a professional qualification    How to apply To apply for this position, download and fill out the application form, and send it to us at the following email address: admin@harmonyprimaryschool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Details</title>
      <link>/contact-us/contact-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact-us/contact-details/</guid>
      <description>Contact Details Locate Us  Harmony Primary School 80 Gayton Road Harrow HA1 2LS  Call Us 0208 427 4688
Email Us admin@harmonyprimaryschool.co.uk
Proprietor&amp;rsquo;s Information  Hillside Educational Trust Harmony Primary School 80 Gayton Road Harrow HA1 2LS </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deputy Headteacher Job Description</title>
      <link>/our-school/vacancies/deputy-headteacher-job-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/vacancies/deputy-headteacher-job-description/</guid>
      <description>Deputy Headteacher          Post title: Deputy Headteacher   Responsible to: The Headteacher and Governing Body   Status: Full time   Pay: Competitive - Depending on experience   Additional benefits: Training and Development allowanceSupport with pursuing a professional qualification    How to apply To apply for this position, download and fill out the application form, and send it to us at the following email address: admin@harmonyprimaryschool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education Support Assistant Job Description</title>
      <link>/our-school/vacancies/education-support-assistant-job-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/vacancies/education-support-assistant-job-description/</guid>
      <description>Education Support Assistant          Post title: Education Support Assistant   Responsible to: The Headteacher and Governing Body   Status: Permanent - Fulltime   Pay: Competitive    How to apply To apply for this position, download and fill out the application form, and send it to us at the following email address: admin@harmonyprimaryschool.co.uk
Application Form  Our Mission Harmony Primary School aims to bring out the best in each individual, striving for excellence on a daily basis; at HPS we lay down strong academic roots as our children are enriched by a broad, balanced curriculum that nurtures their abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expression of Interest</title>
      <link>/admissions/expression-of-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/admissions/expression-of-interest/</guid>
      <description>Expression of Interest Parents are asked to complete an application form to express their interest for entry to Harmony Primary School and, based upon this information, we will commence the applications process once the school has achieved DfE (Department for Education) registration.
Expression of Interest Form </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fees</title>
      <link>/admissions/fees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/admissions/fees/</guid>
      <description>Fees Harmony Primary School is a fee paying school. The Fee Schedule will be updated annually and uploaded here, interested parents are invited to check back for the updated Fees Schedule.
On occasion, the school may make an additional charge for additional activities e.g. trips and visits, which are compulsory to attend for students, but these will always be shared with parents in advance. When such activities are organised they will be introduced compulsorily as part of the school&amp;rsquo;s curriculum experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headteacher’s Message</title>
      <link>/our-school/headteachers-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/headteachers-message/</guid>
      <description>Headteacher’s Message Harmony Primary School is a new aspirational Muslim Independent school in the heart of Harrow; with a passion for Islamic traditions and values we place our students at the centre of our school. Our ambition is to create a school developed upon a spirit of humility and an ethic which instills hard work. Our holistic model of education aims to nurture students into well-rounded, high achieving members of society, prepared for life in 21st Century Britain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home-Learning</title>
      <link>/curriculum/home-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/curriculum/home-learning/</guid>
      <description>Home-Learning Homework, is known as, &amp;lsquo;Home-Learning&amp;rsquo; at Harmony Primary School, it is an integral part of the learning process at HPS. Home-Learning builds on school based learning and improves pupil academic achievement. Homework is an essential aspect of becoming a confident and independent learner, which will help throughout their time at school and beyond.
Pupils are expected to record homework tasks in their School diary during every lesson. Home-Learning is set according to a weekly timetable homework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Curriculum</title>
      <link>/curriculum/our-curriculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/curriculum/our-curriculum/</guid>
      <description>Curriculum Intent At Harmony Primary School we strive to ensure that all children are given a curriculum which is relevant broad and balanced, promoting their emotional, social, physical and intellectual needs. We create a stimulating and inviting learning environment where all children’s interests and learning are fostered using a range of sources to meet the needs of the curriculum. At HPS we wish for all our children to feel safe and secure in their environment, developing self-confidence, independence, self-esteem and an eagerness to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Vision</title>
      <link>/our-school/our-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/our-vision/</guid>
      <description>Our Mission Harmony Primary School aims to bring out the best in each individual, striving for excellence on a daily basis; at HPS we lay down strong academic roots as our children are enriched by a broad, balanced curriculum that nurtures their abilities. Our school harmoniously bring together our children, parents &amp;amp; educators to cultivate an inspiring learning experience rooted in an Islamic ethos.
Our Core Values Community We will seek to foster strong links with the wider community and encourage our children to appreciate differences in age, ethnicity and social background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies</title>
      <link>/parents/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parents/policies/</guid>
      <description>School Policies We are committed to working with parents and other support agencies to cater for the needs of all our staff and pupils.
Below are our policies documents. Physical copies of the policies are available from the school reception.
Behaviour Policy  Code of Conduct  Complaints Policy and Procedures  Curriculum Plans (Year 1 - 6)  Health and Safety Policy  Pupil Assessment Policy  Premises Plans  Safeguarding Policy </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Administrator Job Description</title>
      <link>/our-school/vacancies/school-administrator-job-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/vacancies/school-administrator-job-description/</guid>
      <description>School Administrator          Post title: School Administrator   Responsible to: The Headteacher and Governing Body   Status: Permanent/Full time and Part-Time (Part-time 0.5 Term-time only)   Pay: Competitive    How to apply To apply for this position, download and fill out the application form, and send it to us at the following email address: admin@harmonyprimaryschool.co.uk
Application Form  Our Mission Harmony Primary School aims to bring out the best in each individual, striving for excellence on a daily basis; at HPS we lay down strong academic roots as our children are enriched by a broad, balanced curriculum that nurtures their abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Day</title>
      <link>/parents/school-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parents/school-day/</guid>
      <description>School Day Our School Day commences at: 8:30am
Registration is between: 8:40am - 8:45am
Lunch-Break is staggered between KS1 &amp;amp; KS2: 12 Noon &amp;amp; 1:30pm
Lunch-Break allows for Salah (Prayer)
The School Day ends at: 3:30pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff</title>
      <link>/our-school/our-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/our-staff/</guid>
      <description>Our Harmony Team Come and meet the staff at our school.
From parents and guardians, to support staff and teachers, we&amp;rsquo;re here to help students flourish. But not one of us could do it alone.
As a school striving for Excellence in Education we are delighted to get to know you better and join the vibrant local community of Harrow and North West London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff Vacancies</title>
      <link>/our-school/vacancies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-school/vacancies/</guid>
      <description>Staff Vacancies Thank you for your interest in Harmony Primary School.
We currently have the following vacancies available:
Teaching Class Teacher
Education Support Assistant
Administration School Administrator
Leadership Deputy Headteacher</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Term Dates</title>
      <link>/parents/term-dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parents/term-dates/</guid>
      <description>Provisional Term Dates The dates below are provisional pending our DfE registration, however, potential parents are advised that our calendar will broadly follow Harrow Council&amp;rsquo;s Termly schedule.
Autumn Term 2020
Wednesday 7 Sep 2020 - Friday 23 Oct 2020
Half Term: Monday 26 Oct 2020 - Friday 30 Oct 2020
Monday 2 Nov 2020 - Friday 18 Dec 2020
Spring Term 2021
Monday 4 Jan 2021 - Friday 12 Feb 2021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uniform</title>
      <link>/parents/uniform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parents/uniform/</guid>
      <description>Uniform Our policy is that all children should wear clothing that is in keeping with a purposeful learning ethos. We also believe that certain school activities are facilitated by specialised and appropriate clothing (including organised events outside normal school hours).
Our school uniform will:
 promote a sense of pride in the school; engender a feeling of belonging; be practical and support the safety of children in our leaning environments; identify children with the school; not distract in class (as fashion clothing might be); make children feel equal to one another in terms of appearance; reflect the sense both of community and of diversity that the school takes pride in; be regarded as suitable, and good value for money, by most parents.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>