<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Curriculums on Harmony Primary School</title>
    <link>/curriculum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Curriculums on Harmony Primary School</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="/curriculum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Assessment</title>
      <link>/curriculum/assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/curriculum/assessment/</guid>
      <description>Assessment The National Curriculum has been written to give Age Related Expectations (ARE) for the end of each year. As children travel from Year 1 to Year 6 in our school, they are tracked against the Age Related Expectations. At Harmony Primary School we use RM Integris to support our tracking, the provided us with numbered bands and steps to track children.
The school reports to parents three times a year, at parents evenings you will receive your child&amp;rsquo;s targets based on the RM Integris curriculum linked statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home-Learning</title>
      <link>/curriculum/home-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/curriculum/home-learning/</guid>
      <description>Home-Learning Homework, is known as, &amp;lsquo;Home-Learning&amp;rsquo; at Harmony Primary School, it is an integral part of the learning process at HPS. Home-Learning builds on school based learning and improves pupil academic achievement. Homework is an essential aspect of becoming a confident and independent learner, which will help throughout their time at school and beyond.
Pupils are expected to record homework tasks in their School diary during every lesson. Home-Learning is set according to a weekly timetable homework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Curriculum</title>
      <link>/curriculum/our-curriculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/curriculum/our-curriculum/</guid>
      <description>Curriculum Intent At Harmony Primary School, we strive to ensure that all children are educated through a broad and balanced curriculum: one that promotes their emotional, social, physical and intellectual needs. We provide a stimulating and inviting learning environment where all children’s interests and learning preferences are fostered using a range of resources and pedagogic techniques to meet the needs of an ambitious curriculum. At HPS, we wish for all our children to feel safe and secure in their environment; developing and building upon their self-confidence, independence and eagerness to learn new skills.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
