<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Admissions on Harmony Primary School</title>
    <link>/admissions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Admissions on Harmony Primary School</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/admissions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Apply</title>
      <link>/admissions/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/admissions/apply/</guid>
      <description>Apply The formal applications process will commence upon successful registration with the DfE. However, parents are encouraged to complete the Expression of Interest form in the first instance.
Once the school is operational our applications process will include an Entry Test for all children from year 1 to Year 6, if the child is able to successfully complete this assessment set by the school, then an informal interview with your child and the parents will be arranged with a view to offering a place within our school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expression of Interest</title>
      <link>/admissions/expression-of-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/admissions/expression-of-interest/</guid>
      <description>Expression of Interest Parents are asked to complete an application form to express their interest for entry to Harmony Primary School and, based upon this information, we will commence the applications process once the school has achieved DfE (Department for Education) registration.
Expression of Interest Form  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fees</title>
      <link>/admissions/fees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/admissions/fees/</guid>
      <description>Fees Harmony Primary School is a fee paying school. The Fee Schedule will be updated annually and uploaded here, interested parents are invited to check back for the updated Fees Schedule.
On occasion, the school may make an additional charge for additional activities e.g. trips and visits, which are compulsory to attend for students, but these will always be shared with parents in advance. When such activities are organised they will be introduced compulsorily as part of the school&amp;rsquo;s curriculum experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>