<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parents on Harmony Primary School</title>
    <link>/parents/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parents on Harmony Primary School</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="/parents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Policies</title>
      <link>/parents/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parents/policies/</guid>
      <description>School Policies We are committed to working with parents and other support agencies to cater for the needs of all our staff and pupils.
Below are our policies documents. Physical copies of the policies are available from the school reception.
Assessment Policy  Behaviour Policy  Code of Conduct  Complaints Policy and Procedures  Curriculum Policy  Discipline and Exclusions Policy  Health and Safety Policy  Premises Plans  Safeguarding Policy  Harmony Primary School Prospectus </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Day</title>
      <link>/parents/school-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parents/school-day/</guid>
      <description>School Day Our School Day commences at: 8:30am
Registration is between: 8:40am - 8:45am
Lunch-Break is staggered between KS1 &amp;amp; KS2: 12 Noon &amp;amp; 1:30pm
Lunch-Break allows for Salah (Prayer)
The School Day ends at: 3:30pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Term Dates</title>
      <link>/parents/term-dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parents/term-dates/</guid>
      <description>Term Dates Autumn Term 2020
Term Begins: 7th October 2020
Half Term: 28th October 2020 – 30th October 2020
Term Ends: 18th December 2020
Spring Term 2021
Inset day: 4th Jan 2021
Term Begins: 5th Jan 2021
Half Term: 15th Feb 2021 - 19th Feb 2021
Spring Break: 31st of Mar 2021 - 9th April 2021
Inset Day: 12th April 2021
Summer Term 2021
Term Begins: 13th April 2021
Bank Holiday: 3rd May 2021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uniform</title>
      <link>/parents/uniform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parents/uniform/</guid>
      <description>Uniform Our policy is that all children should wear clothing that is in keeping with a purposeful learning ethos. We also believe that certain school activities are facilitated by specialised and appropriate clothing (including organised events outside normal school hours).
Our school uniform will:
 promote a sense of pride in the school; engender a feeling of belonging; be practical and support the safety of children in our leaning environments; identify children with the school; not distract in class (as fashion clothing might be); make children feel equal to one another in terms of appearance; reflect the sense both of community and of diversity that the school takes pride in; be regarded as suitable, and good value for money, by most parents.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
